{
    "id": "e45064d5017f4413a48d788bb19d51fa",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………… child can learn to sing.",
            "description": "Any and every can both be used to talk in general about all the members of a group.",
            "answers": [
                "Any",
                "Every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eb883a4f9a2f4a6594baace246c5f484"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our birthdays are only a week …………………….",
            "description": "Apart can mean one from another.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "apart",
                "in between"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b4ef78868a974e4c8db5e94563b89403"
        },
        {
            "question": "The weather was unpredictable but we went hiking ………………………………",
            "description": "Anyway means the same as anyhow. Both words mean nevertheless. ",
            "answers": [
                "anyway",
                "anyhow",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8fa9dd0868b14e71a2f05151eb8c9865"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Which color would you like?’ ‘It doesn’t matter. …………………….. one.’",
            "description": "Any can mean this or that or the other.",
            "answers": [
                "Any",
                "Every",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ed62a283a9a48c2a65d2ea4dfdfd668"
        },
        {
            "question": "On the table there were books of ………………………… kind.",
            "description": "Every is similar to all, but all is not possible here because it is used with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "any",
                "every"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "af133d0e7fce4f31834feee3a24f7016"
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t look …………………….. older than her daughter.",
            "description": "Any can modify comparatives. In this case, any is similar to at all.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "all"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef0118461eac4429803132283bb5959c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cooking breakfast is an ……………………. job.",
            "description": "Everyday means daily or common place. ",
            "answers": [
                "everyday",
                "every day",
                "everydays"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1ed1106e88b34c7da6c4f92012dea0c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I read the newspaper ………………………….",
            "description": "Every day is synonymous with each day.",
            "answers": [
                "everyday",
                "every day",
                "everydays"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d96c5664340a48dfa5d951452a270332"
        },
        {
            "question": "Was the movie ………………….. good?",
            "description": "This is similar to ‘at all’.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "93363fa41d64457db04e2281d40cbc4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "My hopes were …………………..",
            "description": "Rise can mean go up.",
            "answers": [
                "rising",
                "arising",
                "Rise can mean go up."
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1cd3ebdcaaca45b0a40d6b5992518d61"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children were running …………………….. everywhere.",
            "description": "Round is used for movement in a circle or curve. Around can refer to movements that are not very definite.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "around",
                "round"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e74cb8f25b2d4d51bfb05822d8e55b38"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t …………………….. to understand his motives.",
            "description": "Seem is often used with can’t. Appear cannot be used like this.",
            "answers": [
                "seem",
                "appear",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "11c4664e7cf84b8a9e54eee030f8808f"
        }
    ]
}